<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Personal website</title><link>https://arseniyshestakov.com/</link><description>Recent content on Personal website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Arseniy Shestakov</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://arseniyshestakov.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Yandex Services Source Code Leak</title><link>https://arseniyshestakov.com/2023/01/26/yandex-services-source-code-leak/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arseniyshestakov.com/2023/01/26/yandex-services-source-code-leak/</guid><description>Just a few hours ago I found mention on Twitter that proprietary source code of Russian giant Yandex been leaked on online community called BreachForums. In this post I&amp;rsquo;ll share results of my friend digging into said archives.
Important details about torrent:
It just content of repository without anything else. All files are dated back to 24 February 2022. It does not contain git history, mostly just code No pre-built binaries for most of software with only few exceptions There are no pre-trained ML models with some exceptions Non-commercial announcement While you&amp;rsquo;re reading this post please consider donating to Helping Hand for Ukraine Relief.</description></item><item><title>Linkedin for Dummies</title><link>https://arseniyshestakov.com/2022/10/19/linkedin-for-dummies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arseniyshestakov.com/2022/10/19/linkedin-for-dummies/</guid><description>Before you start reading I have to warn you: this article is primary written for people new to Linkedin and / or immigrants of war from post-Soviet countries. You probably wont find this article useful if you are citizen of western country with established career and good track record of work experience. People who choose immigration always have to go through a lot of hoops to find a job and specifically one that offer visa assistance and relocation.</description></item><item><title>Update and Inspiration</title><link>https://arseniyshestakov.com/2021/08/04/update-and-inspiration/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arseniyshestakov.com/2021/08/04/update-and-inspiration/</guid><description>Last post I&amp;rsquo;ve posted here more than two years ago. Yesterday I decided to update blog to use newer version of theme, hugo and switch to use Github Actions for deployment. Hopefully now I&amp;rsquo;ll actually start using it as I feel it could be a great tool to improve my own productivity.
Inspiration I&amp;rsquo;ve been working toward sharing more information publicly for a while now starting with my Twitter account, but now I have big goal of trying to do it consistently to report my progress toward being financially independent and building my own business.</description></item><item><title>The Journey of Fantasy</title><link>https://arseniyshestakov.com/2018/12/31/the-journey-of-fantasy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arseniyshestakov.com/2018/12/31/the-journey-of-fantasy/</guid><description>&lt;p>Two years ago, after only ever touching technical literature for many years, I got back to books since their audio format looked like a right way to improve vocabulary. Additionally I wanted to explore modern fantasy as It&amp;rsquo;s was favorite genre of my childhood while I only barely touched it since.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Anyhow I end up listening books almost non-stop especially for the last year and half. Thanks to friends who provided me with recommendations today my reading list is more varied, but I managed to finish plenty of fantasy series. I was never particularly skilled at reviewing specific books and listening with extremely fast pace doesn&amp;rsquo;t help with it either, but I feel it&amp;rsquo;s time to draw some conclusions. &lt;strong>Since it&amp;rsquo;s not really reviews I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to only leave few very minor spoilers in this post so everyone can read safely!&lt;/strong>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How To: pass GPU to VM and back without X restart</title><link>https://arseniyshestakov.com/2016/03/31/how-to-pass-gpu-to-vm-and-back-without-x-restart/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arseniyshestakov.com/2016/03/31/how-to-pass-gpu-to-vm-and-back-without-x-restart/</guid><description>&lt;p>TLDR: If you use FOSS drivers with DRI3 you now can do this:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Use GPU on Linux for any 3D applications.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Pass it into VM and do anything with it.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Once VM is shutdown use GPU on host again.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Everything without reboot and X server restart.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Experimental static website</title><link>https://arseniyshestakov.com/2015/12/23/experimental-static-website/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arseniyshestakov.com/2015/12/23/experimental-static-website/</guid><description>This is my first attempt to create personal website using Hugo.
I&amp;rsquo;m used wordpress for almost ten years and made many projects with it, but for personal website that will be rarely updated it&amp;rsquo;s feels like overkill and ability to host it on GitHub Pages is nice advantage too.</description></item><item><title>About me</title><link>https://arseniyshestakov.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arseniyshestakov.com/about/</guid><description>My name is Arseniy and I am software engineer.
I started my path as freelance web developer, but over years I managed to try a bit of everything. I don&amp;rsquo;t have deep specialization in any specific area, but I know how to get project from idea to launch and further marketing and development. If you want to learn about my coding life please check &amp;ldquo;Not a CV&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Projects&amp;rdquo; pages.</description></item><item><title>Contacts</title><link>https://arseniyshestakov.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arseniyshestakov.com/contact/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m always open to discussion about any projects I participated and happy to make new friends. If you want to continue discussions started elsewhere or just want to ask something please do not hesitate to contact me via:
Email: me (at) thisdomain WhatsApp, Telegram, Viber and other messengers: use phone number in header or @arseniyshestakov Social network URLs are in footer below</description></item><item><title>Not a CV</title><link>https://arseniyshestakov.com/not-a-cv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arseniyshestakov.com/not-a-cv/</guid><description>I am a software engineer who has varying experience across many different areas. I spent almost a decade as a freelance web developer working on existing projects as well as creating my own solutions from scratch. My commercial and personal projects helped me to try many completely different tech stacks.
I love programming and my key strength is ability to rapidly learn anything that required to get the job done. I can work on any OS using any IDE or text editor.</description></item><item><title>VCMI Project</title><link>https://arseniyshestakov.com/vcmi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arseniyshestakov.com/vcmi/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on VCMI engine. It&amp;rsquo;s work in progress open source implementation of Heroes of Might and Magic 3 from 1999. This is one of favorite games of my childhood and I decide to work on it since I was always liked open source projects such as OpenMW and OpenTTD.
Over years I worked on almost all parts of the engine and learned a lot of things about cross platform development, bug testing, continuous integration, packaging and shipping builds for multiple operation systems.</description></item></channel></rss>