<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal website</title>
    <link>https://arseniyshestakov.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Personal website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Arseniy Shestakov</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://arseniyshestakov.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How To: pass GPU to VM and back without X restart</title>
      <link>https://arseniyshestakov.com/2016/03/31/how-to-pass-gpu-to-vm-and-back-without-x-restart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arseniyshestakov.com/2016/03/31/how-to-pass-gpu-to-vm-and-back-without-x-restart/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TLDR: If you use FOSS drivers with DRI3 you now can do this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use GPU on Linux for any 3D applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pass it into VM and do anything with it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once VM is shutdown use GPU on host again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything without reboot and X server restart.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experimental static website</title>
      <link>https://arseniyshestakov.com/2015/12/23/experimental-static-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arseniyshestakov.com/2015/12/23/experimental-static-website/</guid>
      <description>This is my first attempt to create personal website using Hugo.
I&amp;rsquo;m used wordpress for almost ten years and made many projects with it, but for personal website that will be rarely updated it&amp;rsquo;s feels like overkill and ability to host it on GitHub Pages is nice advantage too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://arseniyshestakov.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arseniyshestakov.com/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Arseniy and I&amp;rsquo;m open source enthusiast and C++ developer. I using Linux for over 10 years and have background in web development, Linux system administration and all kind of automation using Bash, Python and Go.
While I enjoy all kind of music, books and TV shows main hobby of my life is PC gaming. Started playing on PC since 1996 and I still huge fan of classical games of many genres from Black Isle, BioWare, Bullfrog, NWC, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contacts</title>
      <link>https://arseniyshestakov.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arseniyshestakov.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m always happy to talk about any projects I participate or continue discussions started elsewhere. Please do not hesitate to contact me if you have any questions:
 WhatsApp, Telegram and other messengers: +44 73 93 026 466 Email: me (at) thisdomain  You can see me on:
 Hacker News Reddit Steam Uber Forums  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not a CV</title>
      <link>https://arseniyshestakov.com/not-a-cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arseniyshestakov.com/not-a-cv/</guid>
      <description>I am a software engineer who has varying experience across many different areas. I spent almost a decade as a freelance web developer, however my personal development projects focus on completely different areas.
Skills and languages  C++: I still consider myself to be a junior developer, I&amp;rsquo;m always learning. Some of the libraries and tools I&amp;rsquo;ve used are:
 Boost, SDL2, googletest. Development of desktop applications: Qt, Qt Creator, GDB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VCMI Project</title>
      <link>https://arseniyshestakov.com/vcmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arseniyshestakov.com/vcmi/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on VCMI engine. It&amp;rsquo;s work in progress open source implementation of Heroes of Might and Magic 3 from 1999. This is one of favorite games of my childhood and I decide to work on it since I was always liked open source projects such as OpenMW and OpenTTD.
Over years I worked on almost all parts of the engine and learned a lot of things about cross platform development, bug testing, continuous integration, packaging and shipping builds for multiple operation systems.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>